{
    "subject": "resource/Her_Grace_Commands",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:German_films",
    "human_readable": "Her Grace Commands is about German films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8832142353057861,
            "question": "Is Her Grace Commands about movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8111332058906555,
            "question": "What type of film is Her Grace Commands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6546294093132019,
            "question": "What is the subject of Her Grace Commands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4909484386444092,
            "question": "What genre might Her Grace Commands belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48850613832473755,
            "question": "What country are German films from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47053655982017517,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about German films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40651068091392517,
            "question": "Does Her Grace Commands deal with a specific topic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39711886644363403,
            "question": "What makes German films unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3966628313064575,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about German cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37422019243240356,
            "question": "Are there any famous German films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Her Grace Commands is about German films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6981_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more information about German cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6981_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes German films unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6981_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Her Grace Commands deal with a specific topic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6981_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6981_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe text mentions that \"Her Grace Commands\" is a 1931 German comedy film, and it also talks about K\u00e4the von Nagy and Willy Fritsch's careers in German cinema. Therefore, the information supports the triple that Her Grace Commands is about German films."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the movie \"Her Grace Commands,\" including that it is a 1931 German comedy film. This supports the statement that \"Her Grace Commands\" is about German films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}